[
  {
    "question": "안녕하세요 (Ahn-young-ha-seh-yo)",
    "answer": "Hello"
  },
  {
    "question": "감사합니다 (Kahm-sa-ham-ni-da)",
    "answer": "Thank you"
  },
  {
    "question": "미안합니다 (Mi-ahn-ham-ni-da)",
    "answer": "I'm sorry"
  },
  {
    "question": "잠시만요 (Jahm-shi-man-yo)",
    "answer": "Excuse me"
  },
  {
    "question": "얼마예요? (Uhl-ma-yeh-yo)",
    "answer": "How much is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "한국말 잘 못해요 (Hahn-gook-mal-jal-mot-hae-yo)",
    "answer": "I can't speak Korean well"
  },
  {
    "question": "반갑습니다 (Bahn-gahp-seup-ni-da)",
    "answer": "Nice to meet you"
  },
  {
    "question": "화장실이 어디예요? (Hwa-jang-shil-ee  uh-di-eh-yo?)",
    "answer": "Where is the bathroom?"
  },
  {
    "question": "도와주세요 (Doh-wah-joo-seh-yo)",
    "answer": "Help"
  },
  {
    "question": "사랑해요 (Sa-rang-hae)",
    "answer": "I love you"
  }
]
